dostiyaari.com 2012-05-06

# Privacy Policy

**Overview**   
dostiyaari.com is firmly committed to the privacy of its members. dostiyaari.com works hard to earn and keep your trust, so it adheres to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

  * dostiyaari.com does not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties. 
  * dostiyaari.com does not share your contact information with other users or third parties without your consent. 
  * Any personally identifiable information that you provide to dostiyaari.com will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology. 

Top

**Information Collection**   
dostiyaari.com is an online marketplace that connects businesses with freelancers. When you visit dostiyaari.com you provide two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by dostiyaari.com and Web Site use information collected by dostiyaari.com as you interact with the dostiyaari.com web site (the "Website"). 

When you register with dostiyaari.com as a user, you provide certain personal information, including, your name, your email address and your address. Additionally, when you establish your profile as a user you will provide information relating to your skills, experience, education level, compensation, work availability, geographic region and self-evaluation. Such information does not identify the specificity of the individual member. Users are not required to, but have the option to display their contact information (i.e. name, address, phone number, email address, etc.) to members who conduct searches of the dostiyaari.com database or use website in general. 

When you enter the Website, dostiyaari.com collects your IP address. This information is gathered for all dostiyaari.com visitors. In addition, dostiyaari.com stores certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. dostiyaari.com uses session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. dostiyaari.com uses a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you return to the Website. dostiyaari.com members must have cookies enabled on their browser. Note, Cookie preferences are set within each browser's Internet options/preferences. 

dostiyaari.com is the sole owner of the information collected through the Website. 

Top

**Information Use**   
dostiyaari.com will not sell or rent any collected information to third parties. dostiyaari.com will not share your contact information with other users or third parties except in connection with possible employment and with your express consent. Accordingly, all registered users agree that certain profile information is accessible to other registered users. 

dostiyaari.com records IP addresses for system administration purposes. This information is used to diagnose server problems, monitor traffic patterns, analyze trends, administer the website, track member user patterns, and identify the most popular areas of the website to deliver content most relevant to registered members. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and are only used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, except in the case of fraud. 

dostiyaari.com reserves the right to share aggregated demographic information with its partners and/or advertisers, such information will not be linked to personal information that identifies registered users, except in the case of fraud. 

Top

**Links**   
The Website contains links to other websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. dostiyaari.com encourages its members to read the privacy policies of all websites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by dostiyaari.com. 

Top

**Changing Your Personal Informtion**   
You can access and modify your personal information by signing on to the website. We will not modify the information provided by you. However, we recommend that you update your personal information as soon as such changes are necessitated. 

Where you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it nor shall you be able to close your account. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on you�re account activity and in accordance with applicable law(s). However, we will retain your personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, Avoid/check illegal and/or potentially prohibited activities and to enforce User Agreements; Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law; Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws; Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation; Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues; Protect the rights, property or safety of dostiyaari and/or its Directors, employees and the general public at large; Respond to Claims of third parties; and take such other actions as may be permitted by law. 

Top

**Account Protection**   
Your password is the key to your account. You shall be solely responsible for all the activities happening under your username and you shall be solely responsible for keeping your password secure. Do not disclose your password to anyone. If you share your password or your personal information with others, you shall be solely responsible for all actions taken under your username and you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

Top

**Links to Other Sites**   
The website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by dostiyaari.com. Please be aware that we, dostiyaari.com and/or the website, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the website or to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. It does not apply to third party advertisements which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such advertisers. 

Top

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

Top
